Ground Control to Major Tom
Take your protein pills and put your helmet on
Commencing countdown engines on
Check ignition and may God′s love be with you
This is Ground Control to Major Tom
You have really made the grade
And the papers want to know whose shirts you wear
Now It is time to leave the capsule if you dare
This is Major Tom to Ground Control
I am stepping through the door
And I am floating in a most peculiar way
And the stars look very
different today
For here
Am I sitting in a tin can
Far above the world
Planet Earth is blue
And there′s nothing I can do
Though I am past one hundred thousand miles
I am feeling very still
And I think my spaceship knows which way to go
Tell my wife I love her very much she knows
Ground Control to Major Tom
Your circuit is dead there′s something wrong
Can you hear me Major Tom
Can you Here am I floating ′round my tin can
Far above the moon
Planet Earth is blue
And there′s nothing I can do