Cool guy with sunglasses slapping a beat on a guitar
Intro
Groovy guitar setting in
Light-weight whistling mixes in with the other instruments
Intro
A guy with sunglasses whistles even more than before
A second, stronger guitar starts playing a funky tune
Intro
The bald Yannic Kilcher with sunglasses on
I'm curling in my sleeping bag
all dressed up in my shower cap
soon I'll be on the largest screen
with my head in a guillotine
My hair smells like an old dishrag
my face looks like a used doormat
my spine is like a horizontal bar
These are just some things you'll find in ImageNet
A thousand cuts of joy, but mostly things to pet
be my weasel
be my pig
be my badger
on an offshore rig
find a beagle
catch a slug
and bring them all to my whiskey jug
watch out for the king snake
the vine snake
the green snake
and don't forget the night snake
the sea snake
and the pug
find a beagle
catch a slug
and bring them all to my whiskey jug
And there I sit, in a rocking chair
looking for my purple hare
what's inside this wooden chest
maybe my bulletproof vest
I hear a border collie cry
A bernese mountain dog goes by
And all the while two hummingbirds stay near
These are just some things you'll find in ImageNet
A thousand cuts of joy, but mostly things to pet
be my weasel
be my pig
be my badger
on an offshore rig
find a beagle
catch a slug
and bring them all to my whiskey jug
watch out for the king snake
the vine snake
the green snake
and don't forget the night snake
the sea snake
and the pug
find a beagle
catch a slug
and bring them all to my whiskey jug
be my weasel
be my pig
be my badger
on an offshore rig
find a beagle
catch a slug
and bring them all to my whiskey jug