Once upon a time you
dressed so fine
Threw the bums a dime in your
prime, didn't you?
People call say 'beware doll,
you're bound to fall'
You thought they were all
kidding you
You used to laugh about
Everybody that was hanging out
Now you don't talk so loud
Now you don't seem so proud
About having to be scrounging
your next meal
How does it feel,
how does it feel?
To be without a home
Like a complete unknown,
like a rolling stone
Ahh you've gone to the finest
schools, alright Miss Lonely
But you know you only used to
get juiced in it
Nobody's ever taught you how
to live out on the street
And now you're gonna have to get
used to it
You say you never compromise
With the mystery tramp,
but now you realize
He's not selling any alibis
As you stare into the vacuum
of his eyes
And say do you want to
make a deal?
How does it feel,
how does it feel?
To be on your own,
with no direction home
A complete unknown,
like a rolling stone
Ah you never turned around to
see the frowns
On the jugglers and the clowns
when they all did tricks for you
You never understood that it
ain't no good
You shouldn't let other people
get your kicks for you
You used to ride on a chrome
horse with your diplomat
Who carried on his shoulder
a Siamese cat
Ain't it hard when you
discovered that
He really wasn't where it's at
After he took from you
everything he could steal
How does it feel,
how does it feel?
To have on your own,
with no direction home
Like a complete unknown,
like a rolling stone
Ahh princess on a steeple and
all the pretty people
They're all drinking, thinking
that they've got it made
Exchanging all precious gifts
But you better take
your diamond ring,
you better pawn it babe
You used to be so amused
At Napoleon in rags and
the language that he used
Go to him he calls you,
you can't refuse
When you ain't got nothing,
you got nothing to lose
You're invisible now,
you've got no secrets to conceal
How does it feel,
ah, how does it feel?
To be on your own,
with no direction home
Like a complete unknown,
like a rolling stone