("Smells Like Teen Spirit"
- Nirvana)
♪ Load up on guns,
bring your friends ♪
♪ It's fun to lose
and to pretend ♪
♪ She's over-bored
and self-assured ♪
♪ Oh no, I know a dirty word
♪ Hello, hello, hello, how low
♪ Hello, hello, hello
♪ With the lights out,
it's less dangerous ♪
♪ Here we are now,
entertain us ♪
♪ I feel stupid and contagious
♪ Here we are now,
entertain us ♪
♪ A mulatto, an albino
♪ A mosquito, my libido, yeah
♪ Hey
♪ Yay
♪ I'm worse at what I do best
♪ And for this gift,
I feel blessed ♪
♪ Our little group
has always been ♪
♪ And always will
until the end ♪
♪ Hello, hello, hello, how low
♪ Hello, hello, hello
♪ With the lights out,
it's less dangerous ♪
♪ Here we are now,
entertain us ♪
♪ I feel stupid and contagious
♪ Here we are now,
entertain us ♪
♪ A mulatto, an albino
♪ A mosquito, my libido, yeah
♪ Hey
♪ Yay
(guitar solo)
♪ And I forget
just why I taste ♪
♪ Oh yeah, I guess
it makes me smile ♪
♪ I found it hard,
it's hard to find ♪
♪ Oh well, whatever,
never mind ♪
♪ Hello, hello, hello, how low
♪ Hello, hello, hello
♪ With the lights out,
it's less dangerous ♪
♪ Here we are now,
entertain us ♪
♪ I feel stupid and contagious
♪ Here we are now,
entertain us ♪
♪ A mulatto, an albino
♪ A mosquito, my libido
♪ A denial, a denial
♪ A denial