(piano playing)
Commander Hadfield (singing): Ground control to major Tom
Ground control to major Tom
Lock your Soyuz hatch and put your helmet on
Commencing countdown, engines on
Detach from Station, and may god's love be with you
(piano playing)
(music swells)
This is ground control to major Tom, you've really made the grade
And the papers want to know whose shirts you wear
But it's time to guide the capsule if you da-a-a-are
This is major Tom to ground control, I've left forevermore
And I'm floating in a most peculiar way
And the stars look very different toda-a-a-ay
For here am I sitting in a tin can
Far above the world
Planet Earth is blue and there's nothing left to do
(acoustic guitar riff)
(music swells)
Though I've flown one hundred thousand miles
I'm feeling very still
And before too long I know it's time to go
Our Commander comes down back to earth and knows
Ground control to major Tom,
The time is near, there's not too long
Can you hear me, Major Tom?
Can you...
Here am I floating in my tin can
Last glimpse of the world
Planet Earth is blue, and there's nothing left to do
(acoustic guitar riffs)
(instrumental)