♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, go, go away ♪
♪ We just wanna party ♪
♪ Party just for you ♪
♪ We just want the money ♪
♪ Money just for you ♪
♪ I know you want to party ♪
♪ Party just for me ♪
♪ Girl you got me dancin' ♪
♪ Dance and shake the frame ♪
♪ We just wanna party ♪
♪ Party just for you ♪
♪ We just want the money ♪
♪ Money just for you ♪
♪ I know you want to party ♪
♪ Party just for me ♪
♪ Girl you got me dancin' ♪
♪ Dance and shake the frame ♪
[gunshot]
♪ This is America ♪
♪ Don't catch you slippin' now ♪
♪ Look what I'm whippin' now ♪
♪ This is America ♪
♪ Don't catch you slippin' now ♪
♪ Look what I'm whippin' now ♪
♪ This is America ♪
♪ Don't catch you slippin' now ♪
♪ Look how I'm livin' now ♪
♪ Police be trippin' now ♪
♪ This is America ♪
♪ Guns in my area ♪
♪ I got the strap ♪
♪ I gotta carry 'em ♪
♪ Yeah yeah Imma go into this ♪
♪ Yeah yeah this is guerilla ♪
♪ Yeah yeah
Imma go get the bag ♪
or Imma get the pad ♪
♪ Yeah yeah
I'm so cold like yeah ♪
♪ I'm so dope like yeah ♪
♪ We gon' blow like yeah ♪
♪ Ooh! Tell somebody! ♪
♪ You gon' tell somebody! ♪
♪ Grandma told me get yo money,
Black man (Get yo money) ♪
♪ Get yo money, Black man
(Get yo money) ♪
[automatic gunfire]
♪ This is America ♪
♪ Don't catch you slippin' now ♪
♪ Look what I'm whippin' now ♪
♪ This is America ♪
♪ Don't catch you slippin' now ♪
♪ Look what I'm whippin' now ♪
♪ Look how I'm geeking out ♪
♪ I'm so fitted ♪
♪ I'm on Gucci ♪
♪ I'm so pretty ♪
♪ I'm gon' get it ♪
♪ Watch me move ♪
♪ This a celly ♪
♪ That's a tool ♪
♪ On my Kodak ♪
♪ Ooh, know that ♪
♪ Ooh get it, get it, work it ♪
♪ Hunnid bands, hunnid bands,
hunnid bands ♪
♪ Contraband, contraband,
contraband ♪
♪ I got the plug on Oaxaca, they
gonna find you like baka! ♪
[frantic footsteps,
faint screams]
[cigarette lighter strikes]
♪ Ooh! ♪
♪ Tell somebody! ♪
America, I just checked my
following list and
♪ You gon' tell somebody! ♪
You motherfuckers owe me
♪ Grandma told me get yo money,
Black man (Black man) ♪
♪ Get yo money, Black man
(Black man) ♪
♪ 1,2,3 Get down! ♪
♪ Ooh! Tell somebody! ♪
♪ You gon' tell somebody! ♪
♪ Grandma told me get yo money,
Black man (Black man) ♪
♪ Get yo money, Black man
(Black man) ♪
♪(Music playing)♪
♪ You just a Black man
in this world ♪
♪ You just a barcode ♪
♪ You just a Black man
in this world ♪
♪ Drivin' expensive foreigns ♪
♪ You just a big dog, yeah ♪
♪ I kenneled him
in the backyard ♪
♪ No that probably
ain't life to a dog ♪
♪ For a big dog ♪
♪(Music playing...)♪