THREE, TWO, ONE.
♪♪ OBIE TRICE
REAL NAME NO GIMMICKS... ♪
- ( record halts )
- ( giggles )
OH-HMM.
♪♪ TWO TRAILER PARK GIRLS
GO ROUND THE OUTSIDE, ♪♪
♪♪ ROUND THE OUTSIDE,
ROUND THE OUTSIDE ♪♪
Marshall,
we've got to boogie.
I'm on the way.
♪♪ TWO TRAILER PARK GIRLS
GO ROUND THE OUTSIDE ♪♪
♪♪ ROUND THE OUTSIDE,
ROUND THE OUTSIDE ♪♪
♪♪ GUESS WHO'S BACK ♪♪
♪♪ BACK AGAIN ♪♪
♪♪ SHADY'S BACK ♪♪
♪♪ TELL A FRIEND ♪♪
♪♪ GUESS WHO'S BACK,
GUESS WHO'S BACK ♪♪
GUESS WHO'S BACK... ♪♪
♪♪ NA-NA-NA-NA... ♪♪
♪♪ I'VE CREATED A MONSTER,
CUZ NOBODY WANTS TO SEE MARSHALL
NO MORE, THEY WANT SHADY ♪
♪♪ I'M CHOPPED LIVER
WELL IF YOU WANT SHADY ♪♪
♪♪ THEN THIS IS WHAT
I'LL GIVE YA ♪♪
♪♪ A LITTLE BIT OF ME
MIXED WITH SOME HARD LIQUOR♪
♪♪ SOME VODKA THAT WILL
JUMPSTART MY HEART QUICKER ♪
♪♪ THEN A SHOCK
WHEN I GET SHOCKED
AT THE HOSPITAL ♪♪
♪♪ BY THE DOCTOR
WHEN I'M NOT COOPERATING ♪
♪♪ WHEN I'M ROCKING
THE TABLE WHILE HE'S
OPERATING ♪♪
♪♪ YOU WAITED THIS LONG
TO STOP DEBATING ♪♪
♪♪ CUZ I'M BACK,
I'M ON THE --- AND OVULATING ♪
♪♪ I KNOW YOU GOT
A JOB MS. CHENEY ♪♪
♪♪ BUT YOUR HUSBANDS
HEART PROBLEM IS COMPLICATED ♪
♪♪ SO THE F.C.C.
WON'T LET ME BE ♪♪
♪♪ OR LET ME BE ME
SO LET ME SEE ♪♪
♪♪ THEY TRIED
TO SHUT ME DOWN ON --- ♪♪
♪♪ BUT IT FEELS
SO EMPTY WITHOUT ME ♪♪
♪♪ SO COME ON AND DIP,
BUM ON YOUR LIPS ♪♪
♪♪ JUMP BACK JIGGLE A HIP
AND WIGGLE A BIT ♪♪
♪♪ AND GET READY CUZ
THIS IS ABOUT TO GET HEAVY ♪
♪♪ I JUST SETTLED
ALL MY LAWSUITS, DEBBIE! ♪
♪♪ NOW THIS LOOKS LIKE
A JOB FOR ME ♪♪
♪♪ SO EVERYBODY
JUST FOLLOW ME ♪♪
♪♪ CUZ WE NEED
A LITTLE CONTROVERSY, ♪♪
♪♪ CUZ IT FEELS SO EMPTY
WITHOUT ME ♪♪
♪♪ I SAID,
THIS LOOKS LIKE
A JOB FOR ME ♪♪
♪♪ SO EVERYBODY
JUST FOLLOW ME ♪♪
♪♪ CUZ WE NEED
A LITTLE CONTROVERSY ♪♪
♪♪ CUZ IT FEELS SO EMPTY
THOUT ME ♪♪
♪♪ LITTLE HELLIONS
KIDS FEELING REBELLIOUS ♪♪
♪♪ EMBARRASSED THEIR PARES
STILL LISTEN TO ELVIS ♪♪
♪♪ THEY START FEELING
LIKE PRISONERS, HELPLESS ♪
♪♪ TILL SOMEONE COMES ALOG
ON A MISSION AND YELLS ----- ♪
♪♪ A VISIONARY, VISION SCAR,
COULD START A REVOLUTION ♪
♪♪ POLLUTIN' THE AIR WAVES
A REBEL ♪♪
♪♪ SO LET ME
JUST REVEL AND BASK ♪♪
♪♪ IN THE FACT THAT I GOT
EVERYONE KISSING MY --- ♪♪
♪♪ AND IT'S A DISASTER
SUCH A CATASTROPHE ♪♪
♪♪ FOR YOU TO SEE SO MUCH
OF MY ASS YOU ASK FOR ME?
♪♪ WELL I'M BACK--
NA-NA-NA-NA-NA-NA... ♪♪
♪♪ FIX YOUR BENT ANTENNAE♪
♪♪ TUNE IT IN
AND THEN I'M GONNA ENTER
INTO THE FRONT ♪♪
♪♪ OF YOUR SKIN LIKE A SPLINTR
THE CENTER OF ATTENTION
BACK FOR THE WINTER ♪♪
♪♪ I'M INTERESTING,
THE BEST THING SINCE WRESTLING ♪
♪♪ INFESTING IN YOUR KIDS
EAR AND NESTING ♪♪
♪♪ TESTING ATTENTION PLEASE♪
♪♪ FEEL THE TENSION
SOON AS SOMEONE MENTIONS ME♪
♪♪ HERE'S MY 10 CENTS
MY TWO CENTS IS FREE ♪♪
♪♪ A NUISANCE, WHO SENT,
YOU SENT FOR ME ♪♪
♪♪ NOW THIS LOOKS LIKE
A JOB FOR ME ♪♪
♪♪ SO EVERYBODY
JUST FOLLOW ME ♪♪
♪♪ CUZ WE NEED
A LITTLE CONTROVERSY ♪♪
♪♪ CUZ IT FEELS SO EMPTY
WITHOUT ME ♪♪
♪♪ I SAID THIS LOOKS
LIKE A JOB FOR ME ♪♪
♪♪ SO EVERYBODY
JUST FOLLOW ME ♪♪
♪♪ CUZ WE NEED
A LITTLE CONTROVERSY ♪♪
♪♪ CUZ IT FEELS
SO EMPTY WITHOUT ME ♪♪
♪♪ A TISK-IT
A TASK-IT ♪♪
♪♪ I GO TIT FOR TAT WITH ♪♪
♪♪ ANYBODY WHO'S TALKING
THIS AND THAT ---- ♪♪
♪♪ CHRIS KIRKPATRICK
YOU CAN GET YOUR --- ------♪
♪♪ WORSE THAN THEM
LITTLE LIMP BIZKIT BASTARDS♪
♪♪ AND MOBY,
YOU CAN GET STOMPED BY OBIE♪
♪♪ YOU 36 YEAR OLD
BALD HEADED STAN ---- ME ♪
♪♪ YOU DON'T KNOW ME,
YOU'RE TOO OLD ♪♪
♪♪ LET IT GO ITS OVER,
NOBODY LISTENS TO TECHNO ♪
♪♪ NOW LETS GO,
JUST GIVE ME A SIGNAL ♪♪
♪♪ I WILL BE THERE
WITH A WHOLE LIST FULL
OF NEW INSULTS ♪♪
♪♪ I'VE BEEN DOPE,
SUSPENSEFUL WITH
A PENCIL ♪♪
♪♪ EVER SINCE PRINCE TURND
HIMSELF INTO A SYMBOL ♪♪
♪♪ BUT SOMETIMES, MAN,
IT JUST SEEMS ♪♪
♪♪ EVERYBODY WANTS
TO DISCUSS ME ♪♪
♪♪ SO THIS MUST MEAN
I'M DISGUSTING ♪♪
♪♪ BUT ITS JUST ME
I'M JUST OBSCENE ♪♪
♪♪ THOUGH I'M NOT
THE FIRST KING OF CONTROVERSY♪
♪♪ I AM THE WORST THING
SINCE ELVIS PRESLEY ♪♪
♪♪ TO DO BLACK MUSIC
SO SELFISHLY ♪♪
♪♪ AND USE IT
TO GET MYSELF WEALTHY ♪♪
♪♪ HEY! THERE'S A CONCEPT
THAT WORKS ♪♪
♪♪ 20 MILLION OTHER
WHITE RAPPERS EMERGE ♪♪
♪♪ BUT NO MATTER
HOW MANY FISH IN THE SEA ♪
♪♪ IT WILL BE SO EMPTY
WITHOUT ME ♪♪
♪♪ NOW THIS LOOKS LIKE
A JOB FOR ME ♪♪
♪♪ SO EVERYBODY
JUST FOLLOW ME ♪♪
♪♪ CUZ WE NEED
A LITTLE CONTROVERSY ♪♪
♪♪ CUZ IT FEELS SO EMPTY
WITHOUT ME ♪♪
♪♪ I SAID
THIS LOOKS LIKE
A JOB FOR ME ♪♪
♪♪ SO EVERYBODY
JUST FOLLOW ME ♪♪
♪♪ CUZ WE NEED
A LITTLE CONTROVERSY ♪♪
♪♪ CUZ IT FEELS SO EMPTY
WITHOUT ME ♪♪
♪♪ HUM-DEI-DEI-LA-LA ♪♪
♪♪ LA-LA-LA-LA-LA ♪♪
♪♪ LA-LA-LA-LA ♪♪
♪♪ HUM-DEI-LA-LA-LA ♪♪
♪♪ LA-LA-LA-LA-LA ♪♪
♪♪ LA-LA-LA-LA. ♪♪♪♪
KIDS!
( music continues )